Guide to the University Archives Poster Collection, 1935-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
- Container List
  - Duke Collegium Musicum presents "Bolognese School of Sacred Polyphony," (no year) April 8 (Box 6)
  - Al Hirt, 1966 April 30 (Box 6)
  - Dance Black Spring Recital, 1983 March 25 (Box 6)
  - Blackburn Literary Festival, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Avner the Eccentric, 1990 December 5-12, 27-31 (Box 6)
  - Quadrangle Pictures, 2001 Spring (Box 6)
  - Quadrangle Pictures, 2000 Fall (Box 6)
  - Marcel Marceau, 1984 February 27 (Box 6)
  - Freewater Presentations, 2003 Fall (Box 6)
  - Science Technology Ethics Policy Symposium, 1982 February 17-19 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - Broadway at Duke, 2003-2004 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - Dissent Past and Present, 2003-2004 (Box 6)
  - Screen Society Schedule, 2003 Fall (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - Quadrangle Pictures, 2003 Fall (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - North Carolina International Jazz Festival, 1995 March 18, 24-25 (Box 6)
  - The Tallis Scholars, 1995 November 28 (Box 6)
  - A Folk Festival, 1995 September 30 (Box 6)
  - Duke Chorale Christmas Concert, 1994 December 8 (Box 6)
  - Defining Duke Recycles, 1993-1994 (Box 6)
  - Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival, 1993 November 5 (Box 6)
  - La Boheme, 1992 November 13-14 (Box 6)
  - Sally Fox on "Histories Denied, Histories Revealed: Documenting Women's Varied Pasts," 1992 March 9 (Box 6)
  - Starting Here, Starting Now (Hoof 'N' Horn), 1992 January 23-25, 29-31 and February 1-2 (Box 6)
  - Quartetto Beethoven di Roma, 1991 November 9 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - Arms and the Man (Duke Drama), 1991 April 2-7, 9-13 (Box 6)
  - Richard Stoltzman, 1991 March 5 (Box 6)
  - Marcus Roberts Trio (Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival), 1991 October 4 (Box 6)
  - The Butterfly's Evil Spell (Duke Drama), 1990 April 4-14 (Box 6)
  - The Servant of Two Masters (Duke Drama), 1990 October 19-28 (Box 6)
  - "A Marvelous Party: The Scenes and Songs of Noel Coward" (Duke Drama), 1990 October 30-31, November 1-4 (Box 6)
  - "The Physician's Art: Representations of Art and Medicine," 1999 November 4-January 16 (Box 6)
  - Earth Week 1999 (Box 6)
  - Broadway at Duke Schedule, 2002-2003 (Box 6)
  - Sexualities in the South, 2003 Spring (Box 6)
  - Quadrangle Pictures, 2003 Spring (Box 6)
  - Blackburn Literary Festival, 2003 February 27-March 21 (Box 6)
  - African Sanctus (Duke Chapel Choir), 2001 April 6-7 (Box 6)
  - Blackburn Literary Festival, 1998 March 2-12 (Box 6)
  - Much Ado About Nothing (Duke Law Drama Society), 1996 March 29 (Box 6)
  - Ballet-Theatre de Bordeaux, 1995 February 26 (Box 6)
  - Miami City Ballet, 1995 October 11-12 (Box 6)
  - Mark Morris Dance Group, 1993 October 8-9 (Box 6)
  - Empire Brass, 1991 November 1 (Box 6)
  - Roy Hargrove (Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival), 1990 October 19 (Box 6)
  - R. Crumb Comix (Duke Drama), 1990 November 6-11, 13-18 (Box 6)
  - Beaux Arts Trio, 1990 October 27 (Box 6)
  - Czech Philharmonic, 1990 October 6 (Box 6)
  - Duke Drama (Box 6)
  - Black on White Symposium, 1988 October 24-25 (Box 6)
  - Conference on Career Choices, 1987 February 14 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - The Challenge of Third World Culture, 1986 September 25-27 (Box 6)
  - Duke Drama, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Freewater Films, 1986 Spring (Box 6)
  - Performing Arts Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Festival for the Eno, 1986 July 4-5 (Box 6)
  - Dance at the Hotel Europa, 1985, April 6 (Box 6)
  - Pinchas Zukerman, 1985 November 19 (Box 6)
  - Dorian Wind Quartet, 1985 February 9 (Box 6)
  - The Duke University Jazz Ensemble with Les Brown, 1985 February 24 (Box 6)
  - The Tokyo String Quartet, 1985 March 2 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - Carmen, 1985 June 8-9, 11 (Box 6)
  - Bernard Malamud on "The Long Writing Road," 1985 March 31 (Box 6)
  - For Colored Girls Who Have Considered Suicide When the Rain is Enuf (Karamu), 1985 February 6 (Box 6)
  - The Hungarian State Symphony Orchestra, 1985 December 2 (Box 6)
  - Vladimir Ashkenazy, 1985 January 22 (Box 6)
  - The Best Little Whorehouse in Texas (Hoof 'N' Horn), (no year) April 5-6, 11-13, May 3-4 (Box 6)
  - Freewater Films, 1985 Spring (Box 6)
  - Fashion Symposium with Mary McFadden, 1985 April 3 (Box 6)
  - The Blackburn Literary Festival, 1985 March 24, 27-28, 31, April 3 (Box 6)
  - Freewater Films, 1985 Fall (Box 6)
  - Agnes of God, 1984 January 31 (Box 6)
  - Danny Richmond Quintet (Mary Lou Williams Festival), 1984 November 29 (Box 6)
  - Freewater Films, 1984 Fall (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - Peacemaking in a Nuclear Age Symposium, 1984 April 5-12 (Box 6)
  - Jean-Pierre Rampal, 1984 February 20 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - Marian McPartland, 1984 or 1985 (Box 6)
  - The North Carolina Symphony, 1983-1984 (Box 6)
  - La Cenerentola (San Francisco Opera Theater), 1984 October 25 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - Rites of Spring (Duke Employee Arts and Crafts Celebration), 1984 May 31 (Box 6)
  - The British American Festival, 1984 June 2-16 (Box 6)
  - James Galway, 1984 November 1 (Box 6)
  - Leontyne Price, 1984 March 30 (Box 6)
  - Torch Song Trilogy, 1984 December 3-4 (Box 6)
  - Summer Theater at Duke, 1984 (Box 6)
  - "The Navajo of Chil-Chen-Beto: Photographs of an Arizona Community" by Roger Manley, (no year) October 2-November 1 (Box 6)
  - Lionel Hampton, 1983 November 18 (Box 6)
  - Freewater Films, 1983 Fall (Box 6)
  - "Lousiana Sugarcane Workers" (photo exhibit) by Debbie Fleming Caffery, 1981 Novembe 2-30 (Box 6)
  - Hildy Tow Paintings and Prints 1983-1984, 1984 August 28-October 3 (Box 6)
  - "The Walker Brothers' 5,000 Mile Journey Across North America," 1984 March 28 (Box 6)
  - The Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center, 1983 October 11 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - New Performing Dance Company, (no year) February 9-10 (Box 6)
  - ArtsFare, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Latent Image Call for Photographs, 1983 (Box 6)
  - The Ciompi Quartet, 1983-1984 (Box 6)
  - Itzhak Perlman, 1983 October 5 (Box 6)
  - Andre Watts, 1983 February 8 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - The Romeros, 1983 February 28 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - Houston Symphony Orchestra, 1983 April 19 (3 copies) (Box 6)
  - Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival, 1983 (Box 6)
  - The Red Clay Ramblers, 1983 April 21 (Box 6)
  - The Folger Consort, 1983 March 26 (Box 6)
  - Duke University Calendar, 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Freewater Films, 1982 Fall (Box 6)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Charles Rosen, 1983 February 26 (Box 6)
  - Energy: A Time for Commitment, 1983 April 11-13 (Box 6)
  - "Life Studies" Exhibit by George Buchanan, 1983 September 28-October 23 (Box 6)
  - Andrew Golden Hand-Colored Xerographs, 1983 August 29-September 27 (Box 6)
  - "Me and Them: Narcissism in an Age of Disengagement" Symposium, 1983 February 15-17 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - The Zagreb Grand Ballet, 1982 November 19 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - Abelard and Heloise, 1982 February 23 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - Duke Artists Series, 1981-1982 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - The Back Aria Group, 1982 November 3 (Box 6)
  - Tsuyoshi Tsutsumi, 1982 April 3 (Box 6)
  - The North Carolina Symphony Pops Concert, 1982 April 14 (Box 6)
  - "Harmony: A Senior Recital in Color" by Bill Haneman and Donna Gregory, 1982 April 4-May10 (Box 6)
  - Loren Withers, 1982 January 26 (Box 6)
  - The North Carolina Symphony, 1982 February 5 (Box 6)
  - Misalliance, 1982 February 24-27 (Box 6)
  - The Enigma (Karamu), 1982 March 18 (Box 6)
  - Claude Frank, 1982 March 16-19 (Box 6)
  - Rites of Spring (Duke Employee Arts and Crafts Fair), 1982 May 12 (Box 6)
  - Richard II, 1982 April 18 (Box 6)
  - Continuum Music Ensemble, 1982 January 16 (Box 6)
  - Lost Eden, 1982 November 7-8 (Box 6)
  - Die Fledermaus, 1982 April 6 (Box 6)
  - ArtsFare, 1982 (Box 6)
  - Freewater Films, 1982 Fall (Box 6)
  - A Raisin in the Sun (Karamu), 1982 November 19-20 (Box 6)
  - One Mo' Time!, 1982 March 2 (Box 6)
  - The North Carolina Symphony, 1982 November 22 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - Guarneri String Quartet, (no year) October 30 (Box 6)
  - Virtuosi di Roma, 1982 February 17 (Box 6)
  - Tintypes, 1982 September 29 (Box 6)
  - "The November Collection: Classic Maya Vases," 1982 October 4-November 28 (Box 6)
  - Crimes of the Heart, undated (Box 6)
  - Porgy and Bess, 1981 April 8 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - The Canadian Brass, 1981 October 19 (Box 6)
  - Kathakali: South Indian Dance-Drama from the Kerala Kalamandalam, 1981 June 3 (Box 6)
  - Artsfare, 1981 (Box 6)
  - Duke University Department of Art Spring Lecture Series, 1981 (Box 6)
  - The Amen Corner (Karamu), 1981 February 27 (Box 6)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1981 March (Box 6)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1981 March 1 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - Richard Selden on "Inflation in the Atlantic Community in the Postwar Period," 1981 March 20 (Box 6)
  - Travesties (1981 April 15-18, 22-25) and The Importance of Being Earnest (1981 April 3-5, 10-12) (Box 6)
  - Quad Flicks, 1981 Spring (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - The William Blackburn Literary Festival, 1981 (Box 6)
  - North Carolina Dance Showcase, 1981 June 22 (Box 6)
  - Madame Butterfly, 1981 February 10 (Box 6)
  - Symposium on the Mass Media in Quebec, 1981 March 2-4 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - Grease (Hoof 'N' Horn), 1981 April 3-4, 8-9 (Box 6)
  - The Ciompi Quartet, 1980-1981 (Box 6)
  - North Carolina Symphony, 1980-1981 (Box 6)
  - Women in Music, 1981 April (Box 6)
  - A Celebration of the Music of Vincent Persichetti, 1981 October 26, 28 (Box 6)
  - Jacques Brel is Alive and Well and Living in Paris, 1981 April 10 (Box 6)
  - Les Ballets Trocadero de Monte Carlo, 1981 March 23 (Box 6)
  - Mimi Garrard Dance Company, 1981 September 27 (2 copies) (Box 6)
  - The Debussy Trio, 1981 October 18 (Box 6)
  - Angela Bofill, 1981 February 16 (Box 6)
  - Five O'Clock Ladies, 1981 May 1 (Box 6)
  - A Christmas Carol, 1981 December 8 (Box 6)
  - Francis Perry, 1981 May 22 (Box 6)
  - City of Women (film), undated (Box 6)
  - Duke University Calendar, 1981-1982 (Box 6)
  - Sugar Babies, 1981 October 29 (Box 6)
  - John Rechy on "The Gay World," 1973 December 4 (Box 6)
  - Dizzie Gillespie (1987 April 4) and Jazz on the Green (1987 April 5), 2 copies (Box 6)
  - box 7 (Box 7)
  - Grateful Dead, (no year) April 2 (2 copies) (Box 7)
  - Grateful Dead Policy (Box 7)
  - Grateful Dead mini poster, (no year) April 2 (Box 7)
  - Allen Williams Scorecard, 1980 December 12 (2 copies) (Box 7)
  - Doug McNeely Scorecard, 1981 January 19 (2 copies) (Box 7)
  - Gordon Whitted Scorecard, 1981 February 21 (2 copies) (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives (Box 7)
  - Duke Basketball Team, 1976-1977 (Box 7)
  - Mike Tissaw Scorecard, 1980 November 18 (2 copies) (Box 7)
  - Basketball Game Programs with Individual Photographs (Including: Gene Banks, Bob Bender, Jim Corrigan, Kenny Dennard, Tom Emma, Chip Engelland, Mike Giminski, Larry Linney, Mike Tissaw), 1970-1980 (Box 7)
  - Duke vs. North Carolina A & T National Invitation Tournament, 1981 March 12 (Box 7)
  - Duke vs. Alabama National Invitation Tournament Round Two, 1981 March 16 (Box 7)
  - box 8 (Box 8)
  - The Fantasticks (Hoof 'N' Horn), November 13-15, 20-23 (Box 8)
  - Karamu Presents "For Colored Girls Who Have Considered Suicide When the Rainbow is Enuf," April 11 (Box 8)
  - Duke Ethnic Culture Day, March 30 (Box 8)
  - Dialog With Black Studies Faculty, March 12, 27, April 9, 16 (Box 8)
  - Mary Lou Williams Jazzfest, April 16-17 (Box 8)
  - Jazz on the Green, September 11 (Box 8)
  - Emporer Delle Ojo and His Cultural Group, November 3 (Box 8)
  - Dance Black "Innovations" Spring Recital, March 20 (Box 8)
  - Barbara Ann Teer (Director, National Black Theater) on "Function of Theatre," April 27 (Box 8)
  - Evenings with Prominent Local Blacks, October 13, 27 and November 3 (Box 8)
  - Stanley Kunitz Poetry Reading, April 7 (Box 8)
  - Anthony Burgess, April 17 (Box 8)
  - Willie Morris Reading, April 9 (2 copies) (Box 8)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, November 15 (Box 8)
  - The George Faison Universal Dance Experience, November 22 (Box 8)
  - New Performing Dance Company, May 18-20 (Box 8)
  - A Day for Dancing, March 1 (Box 8)
  - Seals and Crofts, February 17 (Box 8)
  - Virgil Fox with Revelation Lights, April 6 (2 copies) (Box 8)
  - The Hungarian Quartet, November 3 (Box 8)
  - A Celebration of Spring, April 23 (Box 8)
  - The Clancy Brothers, March 21 (Box 8)
  - Alma Trio, April 14 (Box 8)
  - Candidates Forum with Jim Hawkins and Rev. Lorenzo Lynch, October 30 (Box 8)
  - Student-Parent Graduation Dance, May 6 (Box 8)
  - Chris Paletta ASDU President Platform (Box 8)
  - Evenings with Prominent Duke Faculty, May-August (Box 8)
  - Zazie dans le Metro and A Propos de Nice, undated (Box 8)
  - Duke Wind Symphony Presents A Viennese Ball, February 22 (Box 8)
  - Focus on Contemporary Women, September 29-October 3 (Box 8)
  - Nora Guthrie and Ted Rotante Present "An Evening of Dance Solos and Duets," April 19-20 (Box 8)
  - New York Pro Musica, November 3 (Box 8)
  - Gloria Steinem and Dr. Jewell Greshan on "The Relationship Between Sexism and Racism", April 10 (Box 8)
  - Philip Berrigan on "World Hunger and U.S. Militarism," March 19 (Box 8)
  - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum, November 4-7, 10-13 (Box 8)
  - Grease (Hoof 'N' Horn), April 3-4, 8-9 (Box 8)
  - Shut Up, We're Singing! (Hoof 'N' Horn), January 26-28, February 3, 7, 10 (Box 8)
  - Stop the World, I Want to Get Off (Hoof 'N' Horn), October 27-29, November 4-5 (Box 8)
  - Company (Hoof 'N' Horn), October 31, November 1-3, 6-9 (Box 8)
  - Encore! Hoof 'N' Horn's Celebration of American Musical Theatre, February 27-28 and March 1 (Box 8)
  - Music of the French Baroque (Duke Collegium Musicum), February 19 (Box 8)
  - Collegium Musicum Advertisement (Box 8)
  - Little Me (Hoof 'N' Horn), November 1, 2, 4, 9-11 (Box 8)
  - Carnival (Hoof 'N' Horn), October 28-29 and November 4-5 (Box 8)
  - Godspell (Hoof 'N' Horn), January 19-21, 25-28 (Box 8)
  - Toad the Mime, September 16 (Box 8)
  - Crafts Center Spring Classes (Box 8)
  - Viola Farber Dance Company, 1973 September 21 (Box 8)
  - The Last American Hero, November 12-13 (Box 8)
  - Merrily We Roll Along (Hoof 'N' Horn), November 8-15 (Box 8)
  - Fiddler on the Roof (Hoof 'N' Horn), April 4-5 and May 9-10 (Box 8)
  - Grease (Hoof 'N' Horn), April 3-4 and May 8-9 (Box 8)
  - The Effect of Gamma Rays on Man-in-the-Moon Madness, November 9 (Box 8)
  - You're A Good Man, Charlie Brown (Hoof 'N' Horn), December 1-3, 9-10 (Box 8)
  - Honesty (Hoof 'N' Horn), December 6-8 (Box 8)
  - The National Lampoon Show, undated (Box 8)
  - The Washington Ballet, February 15 (Box 8)
  - Jean Pierre Debris on "Criminal Law and Civil Liberties in South Vietnam" and "The Paris Agreement, Political Prisoners and Peace in Vietnam," November 15 (Box 8)
  - Jimmy Cliff on "The Harder They Come," November 28 (Box 8)
  - "Sins of the Tongue and Diseases of the Will: Books Emblems and Love Songs" by (Box 8)
  - William Van Hittinga, October 14-31 at Salem College (Winston-Salem, NC), signed by artist (2 copies) (Box 8)
  - Stephen Spender, February 2 (2 copies) (Box 8)
  - Cappy Peverall Pottery and Mixed Media Exhibition, February 10-March 1 / Professional (Box 8)
  - Photographers of NC Award Show, February 11-28 (Box 8)
  - Martha Dunigan Prints Exhibition, October 3-31 (Box 8)
  - "The Grand Tour: Turn of the Century Photographs from the Travels of Amelia Burnett" (Box 8)
  - Exhibition, November 27-December 21 (Box 8)
  - Ted Kalmon and Diane Elliot Sound and Movement Performance, February 9 (Box 8)
  - Haitian Contemporary Painting Exhibition, June 10-July 8 (Box 8)
  - "The Real and the Surreal" Exhibition, March 8-31 (Box 8)
  - Jaime Romano Art Exhibition, 1978 October 13-Novemebr 12 (Box 8)
  - James Steward Photography Exhibition, April 24-May 13 (Box 8)
  - Dorothy Aronson and Mark Scott "Abstraction/Distraction" Senior Recital, 1981 May 4-June 1 (Box 8)
  - Duke Seniors Art Exhibition, April 22-May 12 (Box 8)
  - The Rites of Spring (arts and crafts), June 4 (Box 8)
  - "By Faith, the Word Became Flesh: A Celebration of Scripture," March 24-26 (Box 8)
  - The Time of Your Life (City Center Acting Company), January 30 (Box 8)
  - Benny Goodman, October 13 (Box 8)
  - Frank Wilkinson on "Justice in the Nixon Years," November 20 (2 copies) (Box 8)
  - Crafts Center Fall Classes (Box 8)
  - Freewater Summer Series (Box 8)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, February 22 (Box 8)
  - North Carolina Symphony and Duke Chapel Choir, March 30 (2 copies) (Box 8)
  - Duke University Wind Symphony Spring Concert, March 25 (Box 8)
  - North Carolina Folklife Festival, April 19-20 (2 copies) (Box 8)
  - The Private Ear (Summer Theater at Duke), July 12-13 (Box 8)
  - Under Milk Wood (Summer Theater Workshop), June 24-25 (Box 8)
  - A Thousand Clowns (Summer Theater at Duke), June 29-30, July 1 (Box 8)
  - Spoon River Anthology (Summer Theater at Duke), June 22-24 (Box 8)
  - Merton of the Movies (Summer Theater at Duke), June 1-3 (Box 8)
  - Duke Union Schedule, February (Box 8)
  - Reading and Discussion of the Autumn Archive with Reynolds Price, December 11 (Box 8)
  - The Swamp Cats (The New Original Traditional Contemporary Old-Time Sting Band), March 22 (Box 8)
  - The History of Duke Symposium, February 13-15 (2 copies) (Box 8)
  - Ingmar Bergman Film Series, January-March (Box 8)
  - "Chile: La Lucha Continua! (The Struggle Goes On!)" March 24-27 (Box 8)
  - Stewart Udall on "Energy, Environment, and the Remaking of Tomorrow," October 22 (2 copies) (Box 8)
  - New York Philharmonic, 1973 September 14 (Box 8)
  - Dan Rather on "The Shaping of Reality by Television Network News," September 25 (Box 8)
  - Free Beer and a Square Dance, June 18 (Box 8)
  - Duke Ellington Orchestra, September 28 (Box 8)
  - Wayne Lee Voice Recital, October 25 (Box 8)
  - Phi Kappa Psi Celebrity Auction, October 24 (Box 8)
  - City Center Acting Company in Residency, January 29-31 (Box 8)
  - A Concert of Folk Music, October 27 (2 copies) (Box 8)
  - North Carolina Symphony in Concert, September 9 (2 copies) (Box 8)
  - North Carolina Symphony, February 12 (Box 8)
  - Ciompi Quartet, March 1-2 (Box 8)
  - An evening with Iain Hamilton, December 2 (Box 8)
  - Ciompi Quartet, October 26 (Box 8)
  - Mary Elizabeth Turner Piano Recital (Box 8)
  - North Carolina Symphony, December 6 (2 copies) (Box 8)
  - Patricia Goodson (Piano) Junior Recital, March 29 (Box 8)
  - Freewater Thursday Film Series "Great Women of the American Cinema," January 17-April 25 (Box 8)
  - A Jazz Concert, April 16 (Box 8)
  - Freewater Friday Film Series, January 18-April 26 (Box 8)
  - North Carolina Symphony in Concert, November 5 (Box 8)
  - West Side Story (Hoof 'N' Horn), April 1, 3-5 and May 7-8 (Box 8)
  - North Carolina Symphony, September 25 (Box 8)
  - The Durham Civic Choral Society Presents Bach's Mass in B Minor, March 12 (Box 8)
  - Jazz in the Gardens with The Jimmy Wells Quartet, June 24 (Box 8)
  - Campus Tree-Lighting Ceremony, December 1 (Box 8)
  - North Carolina Chamber Players Monday Evening Concert Series, June-July (Box 8)
  - Durham Symphony Concert in the Sarah P. Duke Gardens, June 11 (Box 8)
  - Kilmer Forest and Slickrock Creek 3rd Annual Rededication Assembly, October 9 (Box 8)
  - The Clancy Brothers, March 21 (Box 8)
  - Duke University Chorale in Concert, March 20 (Box 8)
  - Humor Extravaganza, April 14-15 (Box 8)
  - The Gregg Allman Tour, March 17 (Box 8)
  - Die Fledermaus (The National Opera Company) (Box 8)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar (Box 8)
  - Susan Hirschman Flute Recital, April 6 (Box 8)
  - Colloquium on French Organ Music, April 12-13 (Box 8)
  - Birch Bayh on "Justice in American," September 22 (Box 8)
  - Women's Symposium, March 22-April 2 (Box 8)
  - Lindsay Anderson Workshop, March 26 (Box 8)
  - Dave Mason, November 2 (2 copies) (Box 8)
  - Frederic Storaska on "How to Say No to a Rapist and Survive," October 20 (Box 8)
  - The Thief of Paris (Freewater Presentation), April 20 (Box 8)
  - Ten Years After and Yes, November 20 (Box 8)
  - David Crosby and Graham Nash, November 15 (Box 8)
  - Jazz in the Gardens with The Jimmy Wells Quartet, June 24 (Box 8)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream (The New York City Ballet film), September 23, 25 (2 copies) (Box 8)
  - Red Clay Ramlers, Si Kahn, Nee Ningy Band and Bland Simpson in Concert, October 10 (Box 8)
  - David Barison Guitar Recital, October 31 (Box 8)
  - Once Upon a Mattress, March 23-24 (Box 8)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, September-October (Box 8)
  - Marian McPartland Jazz Trio, March 22 (Box 8)
  - The Robber Bridegroom, April 21 (Box 8)
  - Melba Moore in Concert, October 23 (Box 8)
  - A Viennese Ball (Duke University Wind Symphony), October 2 (Box 8)
  - God, February 23 (Box 8)
  - Quadrangle Pictures, January-May (2 copies) (Box 8)
  - The African Queen, June 27 (Box 8)
  - Loggins and Messina, March 30 (Box 8)
  - Steve Forbert, October 24 (Box 8)
  - Dave Mason and Weather Report, November 2 (Box 8)
  - James Stewart Photographs, April 24-May 13 (Box 8)
  - Toys in the Attic, April 17-20 (Box 8)
  - Duke Wind Symphony Kidz Konzert, December 5 (Box 8)
  - The Chuck Davis Dance Company, Inc., July 4, 11, 12, 20 (Box 8)
  - The Duke Preschool and Primary Program Art Show, March 3-26 (Box 8)
  - Surveyor, June 1 (Box 8)
  - Missie Dickens Watercolor Paintings, 1982 September-October 29 (Box 8)
  - Energy 1983 Calendar, April 10-13 (Box 8)
  - Iolanthe or "the Peer and the Peri (Durham Savoyards), April 23-24 (Box 8)
  - Dance Marathon, October 21 (Box 8)
  - Freewater Calendar, January-April (Box 8)
  - Trent Society, 1984 Fall (Box 8)
  - Z, November 30 (Box 8)
  - Edward Dorn Reading, February 14 (Box 8)
  - Bonnie Raitt, January 18 (Box 8)
  - Luther, November 4-6 (Box 8)
  - Duke Dance Group, November 12 (Box 8)
  - Dance Town Hall, July 1-2, 8-9, 15-16 (Box 8)
  - The Wind in the Willows, April 29 (Box 8)
  - Martha (The National Opera Company), May 14 (Box 8)
  - The Washington Ballet, February 15 (Box 8)
  - You're a Good Man Charlie Brown (Hoof 'N' Horn), October 16-19, 24-26 (Box 8)
  - The Fantasticks (Hoof 'N' Horn), 1986 (Box 8)
  - box 9 (Box 9)
  - Camelot (Hoof 'N' Horn), 1977 April 1-2, May 6-7 (Box 9)
  - Football, 2003 (Box 9)
  - Nikolais Dance Theatre, undated (Box 9)
  - Duke University Chapel Choir and Chorale, 1997 January (Box 9)
  - USA-USSR Summer Arts Festival, 1974 July 3-7 (2 copies) (Box 9)
  - Duke Men's Basketball, 2003-2004 (Box 9)
  - Freewater Films, 2005 Spring (2 copies) (Box 9)
  - Duke Reads with Richard Brodhead (2 copies) (Box 9)
  - Duke Women's Basketball, 2001-2002 (Box 9)
  - King Murray, undated (Box 9)
  - David Horowitz, 2006 (Box 9)
  - The Route to Bracketville Starts in Durham (Duke Basketball), undated (Box 9)
  - Duke Women's Basketball, 2005-2006 (Box 9)
  - Duke Women's Basketball, 2000-2001 (Box 9)
  - Duke Reads with Nan Keohane (Box 9)
  - Nasher Museum of Art Opening, 2005 October 2 (Box 9)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theater, 1977 February 10 (Box 9)
  - Duke University Quadrangle Pictures, 1976 Fall (Box 9)
  - The American Masters Plus Series, 1990 June 7-July 21 (Box 9)
  - North Carolina Jazz Festival, 1990 April 1-15 (2 copies) (Box 9)
  - Duke Drama, 1986-1987 (Box 9)
  - Gargoyle Poster, The Chanticleer, undated (Box 9)
  - A Day in the Life, The Chanticleer, 13 November 1992 (Box 9)
  - Chanticleer, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Duke University Artists Series, 1983-1984 (Box 9)
  - Rotterdam Philharmonic, Duke University Artists Series, 1985 (Box 9)
  - New Performing Dance Company, undated (Box 9)
  - Camelot, Hoof'N'Horn, undated (Box 9)
  - Thirteenth Annual Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival, Sonny Rollins, 1996 (Box 9)
  - Twelfth Annual Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival, Marlena Shaw vocalist, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Mary Lou Williams Center, Monthly Schedules, Flyers, undated (Box 9)